fatcatrewards.com 2016-11-04

# Privacy Policy - FatCatRewards.com

###### Ashopfor Pty Ltd (8thfloorads) Privacy Statement

**Last Updated: 19/02/2014**

###### Commitment to Protect your Privacy

Ashopfor Pty Ltd respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it.

Our Privacy Policy explains how and why we collect personal information, what we use it for, and to whom and when we disclose it. We update our policy from time to time, and you should revisit our website regularly to see the latest copy of the Privacy Policy. Any changes will come into effect when the updated Privacy Policy is posted to the website.

In all cases we will treat your personal information with no less protection than that provided for by the Australian and New Zealand Privacy Principles and the privacy laws that are in force in Australia and New Zealand.

###### How and what Personal Information we collect about you?

We collect personal information from you when you respond to one of our programs or request to receive further information from an advertiser. Ashopfor Pty Ltd collects data about you, your interests and subjects you select to receive communications about.

We may also collect information about you from our website but this information will only identify who you are if you provide us with your details (for example, if you provide us with your contact details). When you visit our website our web server collects the following types of information for statistical purposes

  * Your Internet service provider's address;
  * The number of users who visit the website;
  * The date and time of each visit;
  * The pages accessed; and
  * The type of browser used.

No attempt is made to identify individual users from this information.

Before we disclose your personal information to an overseas recipient such as an advertiser or data warehouse:

(a) who is not in Australia, New Zealand or an external Territory; and

(b) who is not the entity or the individual;

we take steps as are reasonable in the circumstances to ensure that the overseas recipient does not breach the Australian or New Zealand Privacy Principles in relation to your personal information.

###### Why we collect Personal Information and what is it used for?

Ashopfor Pty Ltd collects data about you, your interests and the subjects you may like to receive communications about. We also use the information:

  1. To enable us to provide you products and services;
  2. So advertisers you select can communicate with you. Marketing communication might be by email, post, over the phone, SMS/MMS and door-to-door canvassing, depending on which contact channel information you have chosen;
  3. For security and risk management purposes;
  4. To enable us to provide you with information about, and offer you, additional products and services;
  5. To provide to third parties to enable them to give you information about, and offer you products and services.
  6. To enable us to improve the quality of our products and services and to develop additional products and services, and for staff training and quality assurance purposes;
  7. Where a third party has an interest in acquiring part or all of the company, or providing any form of financial accommodation to the company;
  8. To improve the quality and quantity of information on our website;
  9. Marketing analysis.

Where information is provided to any person or organisation other than Ashopfor Pty Ltd you accept that that person or organisation may not have privacy policies that are as protective as our Privacy Policies, and you consent to the disclosure of your personal information with that understanding.

You may opt-out of receipt of any such offers at any time simply by submitting a request via our feedback form or in any way that we notify you in the relevant communication.

###### How we hold your Personal Information

Ashopfor Pty Ltd and/or its third party suppliers hold your personal information on secure enterprise grade servers.

###### To whom do we disclose the Personal Information?

We disclose personal information to our advertisers, customers, third party agents, directors, employees and contractors only for a purpose that is consistent with the way we have informed you that we will use the information in this Privacy Policy.

We may also disclose personal information to any person or authority where we are required to by law.

Other than as we have set out in our Privacy Policy, we will not disclosure your personal information without your prior consent.

###### Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of computer code which remains on your computer and contains information which helps us identify your browser and previous information viewed in relation to our service.

When you visit our website the cookie records certain details including the date, time and advertising content. None of the information in the cookie contains personally identifiable information about you.

If you do not want us to use cookies then you can easily stop them, or be notified when they are being used, by adopting the appropriate settings on your browser. If you do not allow cookies to be used some or all of our website might not be accessible to you.

###### Links to Other Web Sites

Our web site may include web links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content of those other websites, and do not endorse the products, services or information that is on those websites. If you use those websites you should be aware that they will have different privacy policies and terms and conditions of use, which you should review and agree to prior to using those websites.

###### Amending, deleting and how you can obtain access to your Personal Information

We try to ensure that all information about you that we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete and up-to-date.

If you want to obtain access to any personal information and data that we hold about you, or believe any of your personal information that we hold is inaccurate, incomplete or it is not necessary to hold it, you can complete the feedback form, and we will use reasonable efforts to provide it and, if required, correct it. We may charge a reasonable fee to cover the costs of providing personal information to you.

Any enquiries should be in writing to: Ashopfor Pty Ltd, Suite 1308/109 Pitt St, Sydney, NSW, 2000, Australia

You may at any time, request that we delete your personal information from our database by completing our feedback form. If you need us to delete, correct or amend this data, we will do so within 30 days.

###### Security and retention policies

Ashopfor Pty Ltd takes steps to ensure that the information we hold about you is protected from misuse, interference and loss, and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. If Ashopfor Pty Ltd no longer needs the information we will take reasonable steps to destroy the information and/or ensure that the information is de- identified.

If you use the Internet to communicate with us, you should be aware of the risks in transmitting information over the Internet. Ashopfor Pty Ltd does not have control over information while in transit over the Internet and we cannot guarantee its security. Any personal information that we no longer require is destroyed. An exception to this may be where records are retained to comply with legal requirements.

###### Complaints

If you wish to make a complaint or provide any comments on our Privacy Policy please contact us on either: [admin@8thfloorads.com](mailto:admin@8thfloorads.com) or submission through our contact form.

**Ashopfor Pty Ltd**   
Suite 1308/109 Pitt St,   
Sydney, NSW, 2000   
Australia
